# MICHAEL BAUBLITZ

23 Oldfield Court, Middle River, MD 21220 ♦ H: 443-559-8109 ♦ C: (443) 815-8840 ♦ michaelbaublitz09@gmail.com

### Professional Summary

Assembler skilled in managing multiple tasks with frequently changing priorities. Meets deadlines and continuously projects a positive attitude. Very dedicated to my work on hand have done Hvac Systems for 7 years worked with compressors have also worked with multiple trouble shooting steps in Hvac Systems have also did full house installs with hvac ran piping used basic tools such as power drill, hammer drill, screw drivers, wrenches, voltage meter, duct bills, sheet metal cutters. Some advanced tools I used was recovery machines vacuum pump know knowledge on how to reads gauges and where the R-22 and 410 Freon needs to be at on the gauge needles can use a blow torch lift over 50 pounds electrical experience electrical receptacles know how to rewire dimmers, switches.

# **SKILLS**

- Fusing, cutting and measuring tools experience
- HVAC system knowledge
- Knowledge of metal parts and assemblies
- Small parts assembly
- Material packaging
- Materials handling

- Inventory staging
- Packing and scanning
- Team Player
- Safe driver
- Order picking and processing
- Efficient data entry

# WORK HISTORY

# Air Conditioning Technician, 03/2011 to Current

# **Air Conditioning** – middle river

- Obtained appropriate tooling and fixtures.
- Inspected and tested components, assemblies and power tools.
- Wired machines and packages.
- Planned and paced work efficiently in order to meet daily, weekly, project or production goals.
- Observed all safety policies and procedures
- Correctly and safely used a variety of hand tools, saws and cutting equipment to carry out job duties.
- Competently installed foam insulation on tubing and controls.
- Closely inspected parts to ensure they were clean and free of contaminants.
- Ran stainless, aluminum, steel and PVC piping.

#### **Met.** 08/2016 to 01/2017

## **Home Depot** – Cockeysville

- Obtained appropriate tooling and fixtures.
- Maintained counts and lifts, shifts and stocks materials and parts.
- Observed all safety policies and procedures
- Correctly and safely used a variety of hand tools, saws and cutting equipment to carry out job duties.
- Executed the entire assembly process by accurately interpreting set-up sheets, work orders, drawings or blueprints.

# Stower/picker/fork Lift Operator, 03/2017 to 03/2020

#### Amazon – Dundalk, MD

Increased customer satisfaction by resolving issues.

Worked with customers to understand needs and provide service.

Devoted special emphasis to punctuality and worked to maintain outstanding attendance record, consistently arriving to work ready to start immediately.

Transported boxes and product to customer locations in a timely manner.

# **EDUCATION**

High School Diploma: 2014 Kenwood High School Ib And Sports Science - Baltimore, MD